photoreflect.com 2010-10-01

# Privacy Policy - PhotoReflect

## in summary

PhotoReflect is committed to protecting your privacy. Collected information is used to make shopping at PhotoReflect.com possible and to enhance your overall experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. 

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by PhotoReflect and its parent company, Express Digital Graphics, Inc, however, please note all non-transactional information collected will not include any personally identifying information. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of information collection, use, and disclosure. 

PhotoReflect (as a product of Express Digital Graphics, Inc.) is committed to protecting your privacy. Collected information is used to process your orders and personalize your shopping experience. “Required Information” is protected by secure server software. Photos are protected by standard online best practices and can additionally be protected by password and watermark per your or selection (or request to your photographer) during the upload process. We do not disclose your information through sale, trade, or rent to others. 

PhotoReflect welcomes your input; e-mail: [support@expressdigital.com](mailto:support@expressdigital.com) with questions and comments.

**Required Information**

Photography Customers: Name, e-mail address, mailing address, daytime phone number, credit card number, and expiration date are required for all orders. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. 

Photographers: Name, e-mail address, mailing address and payment term (either via direct deposit or check) details are required for all accounts. We may use the information we collect to occasionally notify you of important functionality changes to the Web site, new PhotoReflect services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. When you use the PhotoReflect PhotoCard service, we ask for your e-mail address and that of the recipient in order to complete your request. 

Photographers may request Photo Customer email addresses for additional information. PhotoReflect will never disclose or send promotional e-mail to recipient addresses that belong to the Photographer or that are provided to the PhotoReflect PhotoCard service.

**Protecting Your Information**

Photographers and Photography Customers: When placing orders or accessing your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide features such as storage of items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but in most cases you can change this option in your Web browser. 

**Protecting Your Photos**

Photography Customers: Your photos are organized into events that your photographer can password-protect upon your request. Share your Event ID and password only with those whom you wish to have access to your photos. Friends and family will then have the ability to add your photos to their personal online photo albums and/or order packages that are offered by your photographer. Further, all enlarged representations of your photos on the PhotoReflect.com Web site are digitally watermarked with either "PhotoReflect.com" or your photographer's company logo embedded directly into the images.

Photographers: Any sale of your photography is sold by your policies. You are enabled to password protect events and watermark your photography as you see necessary. The sale of Digital Delivery products enables you to sell your clients digital images for their use. It is at your discretion to opt-in or out of Digital Delivery as well as managing the formal rights of your photography any further use beyond original intention.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

PhotoReflect’s Privacy Policy prohibits selling, trading, or renting your personal information to others. If the Privacy Policy changes to include trustworthy third parties, we will notify you and offer you the opportunity to refuse to share your information. Also, PhotoReflect may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information.
